Mrs Nayak is going to retire soon her
retirement plan often took a back seat
due to family obligations but now she is
ready at age 58 she invests 40 lakh
rupees in ICICI Pro subtle Pension Plan
life annuity with return of hundred
percent of Bocce's price ROP she starts
receiving a guaranteed lifelong income
of 2.75 lakh rupees every year which
includes one percent extra annuity nine
years later she gets diagnosed with
cancer Mrs Nyack informs icic Prudential
life about her illness she receives an
immediate payout of 38 lakh rupees from
ICICI Prudential life on intimation and
her policy terminates which works out to
be 95 of a purchase price be as
financially independent as Mrs Nayak
when you retire be rest assured ICICI
Pro subtle pension plan is backed by
ICICI Prudential life with solvency
ratio of 204.5 percent
additionally enjoy one percent extra
income plan your retirement now from the
comfort of your home buy online now